const words = [
    { front: 'Start!', back: 'Press the next arrow to start the flashcards', diffficulty:"null"},
    {front: "Hallo", back: "Hello", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Tschüs", back: "Bye", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Danke", back: "Thanks", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Entschuldigung", back: "Excuse me", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Ja", back: "Yes", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Nein", back: "No", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Bitte", back: "Please", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Bekomme ich...", back: "Can I have...", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Ich bin hier", back: "I am here", diffficulty:"easy"},
    {front: "Guten Tag", back: "Good morning", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Auf Wiedersehen", back: "Goodbye", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Einzigartig", back: "unique", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Energieriegel", back: "energy bar", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Fernbedienung", back: "remote control", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Frisch", back: "fresh", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Gelee", back: "jelly", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Schön", back: "Beautiful", diffficulty:"medium"},
    {front: "Hinterlistig", back: "Sly", diffficulty:"hard"},
    {front: "Zwielichtig", back: "Shady", diffficulty:"hard"},
    {front: "Gefährlich", back: "Dangerous", diffficulty:"hard"},
    {front: "Verboten", back: "Forbidden", diffficulty:"hard"},
    {front: "Verzweifelt", back: "Desperate", diffficulty:"hard"},
  ];
  
  export default words;
  